路线不变
Hold your line.
保持车速
Keep your speed up,
Dana
Dana.
你做的很好
You're doing great.
既然我做的好 为什么你还是紧跟在
I'm doing so great, how come you're right up
我身后
on my ass?
我要跟着你
I'm drafting you.
不会太久 你跟不上我的
Not for long, you're not.
Jared
Jared?
有点不对劲
Something's wrong.
我刹不住车
I can't brake!
Jared
Jared?
哦 等等
Oh, wait.
我无法控制这辆车
I can't control it!
Jared
Jared!
GA 字幕组
原创译制
翻译：睡不够的饭团、Lily、鸡血
翻译：Echo、Sally、诸事不顺的栗子
校对：阿珂姑娘、流年
总校：流年
字幕分配：鸡血
时间轴&统筹：斯科特栗
NCIS新奥尔良
S03E09
他们已经让你重新穿上制服了 是吗
Got you back in the monkey suit already, do they?
-哦 -制服吗
- Oh. - Monkey suit?
对不起 我以为你是Gregorio探员
I'm-I'm so sorry. I thought you were Agent Gregorio.
哦 你是
Oh. And you are…?
特别探员Dwayne Pride
Special Agent Dwayne Pride,
-NCIS -你好
- NCIS. - Hey.
他就是我跟你说的那个
He's the one I told you about.
哦 那个Dwayne Pride
Oh, the Dwayne Pride.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
我是Hannah Lee 我在联邦检察官办公室工作
I'm Hannah Lee. I'm with the U.S. attorney's office.
换句话说 别惹她生气
I.E., don't piss her off.
我们昨天一起从华盛顿飞过来
We flew down here yesterday together from D.C.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
帮助解决Javier Garcia调查中出现的问题吗
Helping out with the Javier Garcia investigation?
希望能建立一个针对他的个案
Hoping to build a case against him,
我可以因此请求陪审团起诉他
so I can petition the grand jury for an indictment.
擒贼先擒王 要把垄断联盟
Cut the snake off at the head and get the cartel
彻底赶出NOLA
out of NOLA once and for all.
在这他们不说NOLA
They don't call it NOLA down here.
他们更喜欢New Orleans
They prefer New Orleans.
哦 Gregorio 很高兴我们给你留下了深刻印象
Oh, glad to see we made an impression on you, Gregorio.
哦 那是当然
Oh, absolutely.
你带着礼物来的吗
You come bearing gifts?
呃 事实上 Garcia送的
Uh, actually, Garcia does.
波本威士忌 当作是
Bourbon, as a thank you,
帮助我们拯救了他儿子的学校的谢礼
for helping us save his son's school last week.
东西很贵
This is expensive stuff.
我想说这更像是贿赂
I'd say that's more of a bribe.
是啊 为什么我把它送过来
Yeah, why I brought it over.
我想你们会把它当作证物记录
Thought you'd want to log it as evidence.
Sebastian怎么样了
How's Sebastian?
我敢说 成为团队中的一员 他很兴奋 对吧
I bet he's so excited to be a part of the team, huh?
暂时还不是 还要通过联邦执法培训中心的测试
Not part of it yet, still has to make it through FLETC training,
这意味着 在他通过测试前 我们还是人手不足
which means, until he does, we're short-handed again.
很抱歉让你处于困境
I'm sorry to leave you high and dry.
没事
Yeah.
但是如果你需要任何帮助 就通知我 好吗
But look, if you need any help, just let me know, all right?
好的
Okay.
很可惜我不认为你能去
Except that I don't think that you can.
Isler主任跟我说得很清楚
Director Isler made it pretty clear to me
我们只是来这里建立
that we are only down here to build
针对Garcia的个案
the case against Garcia,
然后就安心回华盛顿
and then it's back to D.C. for good.
好吧 我明白了 这是个重要的案子
Well… I get that. It's an important case.
我得走了 Lee女士 很高兴见到你
I gotta go. Nice to meet you, Ms. Lee.
嘿 替我向他们每个人问好 行吗
Hey, tell everyone I said hi, okay?
好的 肯定
Yeah, you bet.
再见
Bye.
我们继续工作
Let's get back to work.
被害人是Jared Connors下士 28岁
The victim is Corporal Jared Connors, 28,
第四陆战师
Fourth Marine Division.
休假的时候 他会定期到这里赛车
Drove here regularly when he was on leave,
他甚至在参加过几次业余赛车比赛
he even raced in the amateur circuit a few times.
-老司机了 -很显然是
- Experienced driver. - Apparently.
他和他的女朋友 Dana Wells
Him and the girlfriend, Dana Wells,
是车祸发生时在赛道上仅有的车手
were the only drivers on the track when he crashed.
他的车失去了控制吗
Lost control of his car?
是的 除了他的父亲认为他是被谋杀的
Yeah, except his father thinks he was murdered.
Russ Connors是某个赛车团队里的机修工
Russ Connors is a mechanic on one of the racing teams.
他告诉当地警官 他确信车被蓄意破坏
Told the sheriffs he's convinced the car was sabotaged.
蓄意破坏 他为什么这么想
Sabotage? Why does he think that?
我还没跟他说上话
Well, I didn't get to talk to him.
他为了把儿子从残骸中拖出来 受伤严重 所以
He got cut pretty bad taking his son out of the wreck, so…
医务人员把他跟他儿子的女朋友都送往医院了
Paramedics took him and the girlfriend to the hospital.
你觉得那跟案子有关吗
Think that's case-related?
更像是情侣吵架
More like trouble in paradise.
我觉得目前他跟Melody处得并不好
I don't think he and Melody are getting along right now.
好吧 这很不容易
Well, it can't be easy…
这个女人突然闯进他的生活 还捎带个孩子 吓了他一跳
Woman pops into his life, surprises him with a baby.
至少Lasalle正努力去做正确的事情
At least Lasalle's trying to do the right thing.
我只希望不要太影响他的工作
Just wish it didn't affect his work so much,
特别是在人员不足的情况下
undermanned as it is.
Christopher
Christopher!
死因看起来是
Cause of death appears to be
头部 颈部 胸部的钝力外伤
blunt force trauma to the head, neck, chest.
符合时速100英里以上造成的冲击
It's consistent with an impact of over 100 miles an hour.
哦 看来他一直没有减速
Oh, it's like he never slowed down.
唯一好消息是
And the only silver lining is
死亡很可能就在一瞬间
the death is likely instantaneous.
他没怎么受罪
He didn't suffer.
有可能是他的身体状况造成的吗
Possible he had a medical condition?
心脏病发作 中风
Heart attack? Stroke?
他很年轻 但是尸检后我会有进一步了解
He's awfully young. But I'll know more after the autopsy,
我会做一个兴奋剂检验来检测药物和酒精
and I'll do a tox screen for drugs and alcohol.
你好 老大
Hey, boss.
哦 等一下 没人叫你“老大”
Oh, wait, nobody calls you "boss,"
对吧 这太随意了
do they? It's too informal.
我懂了 一段崭新的关系不该就这样开始
I get it, it's no way to start a relationship.
Sabastian 我们不用开始什么关系 好吗
Sebastian, we're not starting a relationship, okay?
我们都认识好多年了
We've known each other for years.
是的 但不是雇主和雇员的关系
Yeah, but not as employer and employee.
那是截然不同的互动 长官
That's a whole different dynamic, sir.
“长官”听起来好像也不对
"Sir" doesn't sound right, either.
你确定要让这家伙成为探员吗
You sure about making this guy an agent?
我认为这很伤人 你知道吗 现在
I find that hurtful, you know, right here.
Sebastian 案子
The case, Sebastian.
对 好的 呃
Right. Yeah, well, uh,
这很简单 我认为 至少从表面上看
it's really simple, I guess, at least on the surface.
车开得太快 没有办法转弯
Car was going too fast, couldn't make the turn.
这种情况不需要复杂的鉴证
Don't really need fancy forensics
就能搞明白
to figure that part out.
有被破坏的迹象吗
Any signs of sabotage?
还没有 我会把车送到证据库
Not yet. But I'll have the car transported
我要做一个完整的司法鉴定
to the evidence garage, I'll do a full forensic work-up.
当然 除非你们需要我待在这儿
Unless, of course, you need me to stay here.
询问目击者 彻底检查这片区域
Interview witnesses, canvass the area.
因为我一直忙于跟上
'Cause I am totally up to speed on
NCIS调查手册的进度
the NCIS investigation manual.
我需要你来完成检测
And I need you to finish the examination.
暂时 你还是要为我工作的 记得吗
You still work for me, for now, remember?
我马上照办 老大
You got it, boss.
Loretta 我们不会让你人手不够的
We're not gonna leave you undermanned, Loretta.
Sebastian走出实验室后仍然是为你工作的
Sebastian can still work out of the lab for you,
甚至在他成为一名特别检验探员后也一样
even after he becomes a special forensics agent.
只希望有人能提前告诉我
Just wish somebody had told me in advance.
哦 King 抱歉
Ooh, sorry about that, King.
不会再发生了
Won't happen again.
以后再说
Talk about it later.
你对竞速车有研究
You got experience tracking cars.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
没什么很有用的
Well, not a lot that makes sense,
尤其是这些打滑的痕迹
especially with these skid marks.
赛车手知道在转弯处控制车辆滑动
Racers know to control their slides around turns,
但是这些表明Jared出于某种原因
but these indicate that Jared kept accelerating
不断加速 然后失去了控制
for some reason, and then lost it.
也许他的油门卡住了吧
Well, maybe his accelerator stuck.
有可能
It's possible,
但是这些打滑痕迹不是刹车造成的
but these skid marks are inconsistent with braking,
这就引出了一个问题 他为什么不刹车
which begs the question, why didn't he?
希望Sebastian能给我们解答
Well, hopefully Sebastian will be able to give us some answers.
同时 让我们查明关于
Meanwhile, let's find out everything we can
这个海军的一切
about our marine.
确保他没有什么见不得人的秘密
Make sure he doesn't have any skeletons in his closet.
-可以指望你吗 -当然
- Count on you? - Absolutely.
好的 Percy和我去医院
All right, Percy and I are gonna head over to the hospital,
跟Jared的父亲谈谈
talk to Jared's father.
看看能否跟我们解释下 他认为儿子是被谋杀的原因
See if he can explain to us why he thinks his son was murdered.
我不知道为什么我会说车被蓄意破坏
I-I-I don't know why I said it was sabotage.
我当时头脑混乱
I wasn't thinking straight.
我只是很难过 仅此而已
I was just upset, that's all.
但是 Connors先生 你一开始就认为是人为破坏
But, Mr. Connors, there has to be a reason
总得有个理由吧
you thought initially that it was sabo…
我说了我脑子很乱 行了吗
I said I wasn't thinking. Okay?
我的儿子刚去世
My son just died.
Connors先生
Mr. Connors,
我无法想象这对你而言有多痛苦
I can't imagine how difficult this must be for you,
可我们的工作是查出当时你儿子到底经历了什么
but our job is to find out what happened to your son.
你能理解的 对么
You know that, right?
是的 当然了
Sure. Of course.
那你知不知道为什么
Do you know of any reason why
有人可能害死Jared
somebody might have wanted to hurt Jared?
我 我不知道
I-I don't know.
那你呢 Wells女士
What about you, Ms. Wells?
你当时发现什么可疑的情况了吗
Did you see anything suspicious?
没有
No.
我们当时正在跑道上相互追逐
We were just chasing each other around the track,
你懂的 玩得很疯
you know, messing around.
Jared当时正在教我怎样赛车
Jared was showing me how to race.
这么说这是你第一次赛车
So it was your first time.
我以前参加过赛车比赛
I've been in racecars before.
我是Warbury赛车比赛的高级协调员
I'm the advance coordinator for Warbury Racing.
这周我们来到镇上是为了参加比赛
We're in town this week for the race.
你们俩都为同一支队伍效力吗
You two work for the same team?
对 差不多有一年了 没错
Yeah, about a year now, yeah.
我是这样认识Jared的
That's how I met Jared.
自那以后我们就开始约会
We've been dating ever since.
-他开车技术如何 -车技非常棒
- Was he a good driver? - He was great.
他一生都在赛车
Well, he's been racing his whole life.
从驾驶单座赛车开始
All the way back to go-carts.
他原本计划退伍后立刻成为职业赛车手
He was gonna turn pro after his discharge.
是不是机械故障导致的事故
Possible it was mechanical failure?
不 不可能 那辆赛车是我们自己组装的
No, no, no, we built that car ourselves.
每次驾驶前我们都会从头到尾仔细检查
Check it out head to toe every time we took it out.
那么我不得不问
Then I have to ask,
Jared有没有为一些事感到沮丧 情绪低落
was Jared upset about anything? Depressed?
没有 他不是故意翻车的 如果你在暗示这个的话
No, he didn't crash on purpose, if that's what you're implying.
好吧 那么
Okay, so…
抱歉 如果不是故意为之
Sorry. If it wasn't intentional,
也不是驾驶失误或机械故障
and it wasn't driver or mechanical error,
那翻车的原因是什么呢
what caused the crash?
我不知道
I don't know!
他们显然在隐瞒什么
Well, they're obviously hiding something.
问题是 隐瞒了什么 为什么要隐瞒
The question is, what and why?
根据他们共同维护Jared的表现来看
Either they're complicit, which based on how they were
要么是他们串通好了 这很难令人相信 要么是
both defending Jared, it's hard to believe, or…
因为某种原因 他们非常害怕 不敢说出来
They're too scared to talk for some reason.
没错 这就意味着不管现在能否得到他们的帮助
Yeah. Which means we're gonna have to figure out the truth,
我们都要查出真相
with or without their help for now.
Loretta得到了尸检结果
Loretta's got autopsy results.
我过去看看她有什么发现
I'll see what she's found.
也许你应该和Christopher会合
Maybe you should catch up with Christopher,
搜查Jared的家 看看能否找到线索
go through Jared's house, see if you can find any leads.
我认为我们暂时
I don't suppose we could ask Gregorio
还不能让Gregorio帮忙 因为
to pitch in temporarily, seeing as though
我们的线索非常少
we're spread pretty thin.
不 我不会指望这个
No, I wouldn't count on it.
Gregorio正在帮助联邦律师
Gregorio's helping the U.S. attorney
准备针对Garcia的公诉书
build an indictment against Garcia.
她用不了多久就该回去了
It won't be long before she's heading home.
最好随她去吧 打起精神 我们还有很多东西要查
Best let her be. Come on. We've got things to learn.
毒性分析仪没有检测出任何有毒物质
A prelim tox screen was negative for any anomalies,
除非你能拿出其他证据
so unless you come up with something else,
否则我只能断定他是意外死亡
I'm ruling his death as accidental.
你让我大老远过来 就是为了跟我说这个
You brought me all the way out here just to tell me that?
不是 因为我觉得这不是意外
No. Because I don't think it was an accident,
主要是因为这个
mainly because of this.
很显然 这位海军是曾被人捅伤的
Apparently, your marine was stabbed,
根据肉芽组织
and based on the granulation tissue
和恢复的情况来看
and the degree of healing,
我认为发生在三四天前
I'd say this happened three or four days ago.
他自己缝合的伤口么
He stitch himself up?
看起来是
Appears so.
他本该去医院的
Should've gone to the hospital.
伤口很深 可他没去
It's a pretty deep wound, but he didn't go.
说明他不希望外界发现
That means he didn't want the authorities
是谁捅伤的他
to find out who stabbed him.
如果这次袭击在某种程度上和
And if this attack is somehow connected
翻车死亡有关联 那么
to the crash that killed him, then…
正如我所说
Like I said,
这不是意外事故
it's not an accident.
所有人都隐瞒某件事
Everybody's hiding something about this case.
很显然 Jared也是
Apparently, even Jared.
哪儿都一样
That seems to be going around.
Loretta 我很抱歉
Loretta… I'm sorry.
我并没有和你隐瞒什么
But I wasn't hiding anything from you.
我当时以为Sebastian在找我之前会先来找你
I assumed that Sebastian came to you before he came to me.
事实是 我先向Gregorio发出职位邀请
Truth is, I'd offered the position to Gregorio first.
但她拒绝你了么
And she turned you down?
不太适合她吧 我猜
Wasn't the right fit for her, I guess.
所以当Sebastian说他想当探员时
So when Sebastian surprised me,
我感到很吃惊 我…
said he wanted to become an agent, I…
Dwayne 我没有生你的或Sebastian的气
Dwayne, I'm not mad at you or Sebastian.
我一直都知道 他迟早要离开这儿
I always knew he'd come out of his shell sooner or later.
事实是
The truth is,
我觉得 如果我是你的话 需要更加担心的是
I think you need to worry more about
Sebastian在出外勤时会让你发疯
Sebastian driving you crazy in the field, if I were you.
很有可能是这样
Good possibility of that.
好了 去吧 你还有很多事要做
Come on, go. You got your hands full.
你也不用担心我
You don't have to worry about me, too.
对你我一直都有时间 Loretta
I always got time for that, Loretta.
这有超过10万美金现金了 对吧
There must be over $100,000 in here, huh?
对于一个年薪刚到3万美元的下士来说
That's a lot of cash for a corporal
是笔巨款了
that barely clears 30 thou a year.
-你认为这钱不干净 -应该是的 对吧
- You think it's dirty? - It's gotta be, right?
我是说 要不Jared怎么会
I mean, why else would Jared hide
把这么多现金藏到车库呢
this much cash in his garage?
还有 这钱他从哪得来的
Plus, where'd he get it?
可能是他抢银行得来的
Maybe he stole it from a bank.
这看上去像是染料包爆炸了
This looks like a dye pack went off.
嗯 显然我们这位海军并不像他表面上看起来这么清白
Hmm, apparently our marine isn't as squeaky-clean as he seems.
好吧 查出真相的唯一方法就是
Well, only way to find out is
找出钱是从哪里来的
to figure out where the cash came from.
FBI专查银行抢劫案
FBI specializes in bank robberies.
我过会儿把序列号发给Gregorio
Maybe I'll send Gregorio the serial numbers,
-看看她能否查到来源 -Gregorio
- see if she can trace 'em. - Gregorio?
我们不是应该不再让她参与了吗
Aren't we supposed to leave her alone?
简单查查而已 就一分钟的事
It's just a quick check. It won't take her a minute.
-好吧 呵呵 -呵呵
- Yeah, uh-huh. - Uh-huh.
Lasalle 你认识他们吗
Lasalle, you know these people?
Melody 你来这里干什么
Melody, what are you doing here?
很抱歉 Chris 我跟他说了别来 但是…
I'm sorry, Chris, I told him not to come, but…
你是谁
Who are you?
嘿
Hey!
孩子的父亲 就是我
The baby's father! That's who I am!
离我儿子远点儿
Stay the hell away from my son!
-手背到后面 快点 -混蛋
- Bend your arms now! - Son of a bitch!
Melody 跟我说
Melody, talk to me.
他说的是真的吗 Tucker不是我儿子
Is he telling the truth? Is Tucker not my son?
你要相信我 我从没想过要伤害你
You gotta believe me, I never meant to hurt you.
这话是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你为什么要对我说谎
Why did you lie to me?
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
Melody
Melody!
听着 在警察来之前先把他关到审讯室
Look, put him in interrogation until NOPD comes.
-放他走吧 -什么
- Let him go. - Do what?
听着 我刚说了放他走 见鬼
Look, I said just let him go, damn it.
如果我是他 我很可能也会这样做
I probably would have done the same thing if I were him.
-Lasalle… -听着 放了他
- Lasalle… - Look, just do it!
离我的孩子远点
Stay the hell away from my kid.
在我改变主意以前离开这里
Get out of here before I change my mind.
你相信他
You believe him?
我不知道该相信什么
I don't know what to believe.
但Melody对此似乎清楚
Melody did seem pretty clear about it, though.
我是说 她一直不停地说她很抱歉
I mean, she kept saying she was sorry.
她怎么能这样做呢 King
I mean, how could she do it, King?
把一个小男孩带到我的生活里告诉我
Bring a little boy into my life
我是他的父亲 但其实不是
and tell me I'm his father… when I'm not?
我不知道 Chris
I don't know, Chris.
有些事情你得问她
Something you gotta ask her.
这也改变不了什么 这么做又有什么意义
Well, it won't change anything, so what's the point?
意义是 你有权利知道
The point is, you deserve to know.
无所谓了 行了 事实就是这样
It doesn't matter, all right, it is what it is.
Christopher
Christopher.
这件事不是你假装没发生就可以算了的
It's not something you can pretend didn't happen.
你放走那个揍你的人已经够糟糕的了
It's bad enough you let the guy go.
没什么大不了的
It wasn't a big deal.
袭击联邦警察一直是很恶劣的行为
Assaulting a federal officer is always a big deal,
这你知道
and you know it.
但实际上你并没有逮捕他
The fact that you didn't arrest him
我觉得你头脑不清醒
tells me you're not thinking straight.
听着 不要担心我 King
Look, don't worry about me, King.
好吗 我没事
All right? I'm fine.
我们回去工作吧
Let's just get back to work.
打断一下 关于被偷的钱
Sorry to interrupt, but we just got a lead
有了新线索
on the stolen money.
好 我去查
Yeah, I'm on it.
我什么也没见 线索在哪儿
I don't see anything. Where's the lead?
确切的说不是我的线索
Well, it's actually not my lead, so…
你去了好久 Percy
Took you long enough, Percy.
我也不是整天都有时间
I don't exactly have all day.
哎 抱歉 有事情耽误了
Yeah, sorry, something came up.
-你通知了Gregorio -发了个邮件
- You called Gregorio. - E-mailed.
只是一些序列号
And it was just some serial numbers,
这都是她自己的选择
so this was all her choice.
不是什么大事 Pride 怎么说 事实上也算是吧
It's not a big deal, Pride. Well, actually it is.
这些钱来自一起银行劫案
The bills came from a bank robbery
密西西比的Biloxi 六周前
in Biloxi, Mississippi, six weeks ago.
在劫犯们把钱抢走之前
A teller slipped a dye pack into the money
一个出纳把染色包顺进了现金里
before the robbers took off.
看上去我们的海军成了银行劫匪
Seems that makes our marine a bank robber.
但这不能解释Jared为何被捅伤
Doesn't explain why Jared was stabbed
以及是谁会谋杀他
or who'd want to kill him.
Biloxi案子有多少劫犯
How many robbers in Biloxi?
目击者说有四人
Witnesses said there were four,
包括一个逃走的全副武装的司机
including a getaway driver, heavily armed, too.
所以 劫犯们开始内讧了
So, robbers turning against each other?
-怎么了 -噢 嘿 Hannah
- What's going on? - Oh, hey, Hannah.
Pride探员
Agent Pride.
我希望你们在讨论与贩毒集团有关的案件
This is about the cartel case, I hope?
我得走了 再会
Gotta go. Bye.
哇哦
Whoa.
希望我们没给她找麻烦
I hope we didn't get her in trouble.
-呃 不是“我们” 只有你 -就是个邮件而已
- Uh, not "we," you. - It was just an e-mail.
再怎么说 这给我们提供了一个线索 不是吗
Anyway, it got us a lead, didn't it?
是啊 没准还让Gregorio被解雇了
Yeah, and possibly Gregorio fired.
我知道我们都怎么看待Gregorio的
I know how we all feel about Gregorio,
但是我们得习惯没有她一起工作的日子了 好吗
but we gotta learn to work without her again, okay?
好吧
Okay.
从查明
Starting with figuring out
Jared是如何牵扯进银行抢劫案开始
how, exactly, Jared's connected to the bank robbery.
也许就是他父亲和女友在隐瞒的事情
Well, it may be what his father and girlfriend were hiding.
我是说 Dana看起来非常紧张
I mean, Dana seemed really nervous.
我们再去找他们谈谈
Let's have another chat with them.
只不过这次要分开谈
Only separately this time.
Sebastian好像在车上找到了些什么
Looks like Sebastian's found something on the car.
我去看看
I'll check it out.
他还好吧
Is he okay?
不知道
Don't know.
帮个小忙 可以不
Little help, please?
呃 谢谢
Ah, thank you.
天啊 腰酸背痛
Man, I am sore.
这就是我一直在为海军罪案调查处的训练
It's gotta be all that ab work I've been doing
做的准备 你知道吧
prepping for NCIS training, you know?
哇噢 你介意把那玩意儿关掉吗
Whoa. You care to turn that off, please?
什么 噢 好吧 抱歉
What? Oh, right. Sorry.
这位美人怎么了
So what about this beauty?
嗯 我对这辆车的残骸
Uh, I went over what's left of the car
进行了彻底的检查
with a fine-tooth comb.
我没有找到任何证据
I didn't find any evidence
证明是机械故障或者蓄意破坏
of a mechanical problem or even sabotage.
-但是 -但是
- But? - But…
当我运行了一个全套诊断程序
when I ran a full diagnostic
在这辆车的控制器局域网络
on the car's controller area network--
那个网络就像是 大脑中枢
that's, like, the brain.
这些天几乎控制了这辆车的所有行动
Pretty much controls everything in the car these days.
控制器局域网络 我知道 是个电脑吧
The CAN, I know. It's a computer?
对 就像所有电脑一样
Right, and just like any computer,
可以用新的软件进行升级
it can be upgraded with new software
但是也会被黑掉
but it can also be hacked--
用来完成黑客的所有要求
made to do whatever the hacker wants it to do.
比如用油门替换刹车
Like accelerate instead of brake?
是啊 对这个案子来说 是这样
Yeah, in this case, exactly.
有人用无线操控
Somebody overrode the accelerator module
改动了加速模块
wirelessly.
让它持续加速
Told it to keep going faster.
如果在合适的时机完成改动 司机完全无能为力
If done at the right time, there's nothing a driver can do.
合适的时机就是
And the right time is just as
Jared进入弯道的时候
Jared entered the turn,
这意味着他确实是被谋杀的
which means he was definitely murdered.
是啊 也意味着不管是谁干的
Yeah, it also means that whoever did this
他们完全清楚自己在做什么
knows exactly what they're doing.
不是吧 她在干什么
No, what is she doing?
嗯 怎么了
Why, what's up?
没事 但是我得走了
Never mind. But I gotta go.
嘿 告诉Pride你查出的结果 行吗
Hey, fill in Pride on what you found out, all right?
噢 好的
Uh… okey-dokey.
那是Scott Hamilton
And that's Scott Hamilton…
我希望我能帮助你 真的
I wish I could help you, I do,
但我确实不知道
but I don't know how.
不 你知道的 Dana
Yes, you do, Dana.
你是Jared的女友 你不可能
There's no way you're Jared's girlfriend
一无所知
and didn't know something.
Dana 你的男友是被谋杀的
Dana, your boyfriend was murdered.
你对此竟无动于衷吗
Doesn't that matter to you?
当然不是 但是我要去
Of course it does, but I'm not gonna…
Dana 我们刚刚发现
Dana! We just found out
我们失去了排位赛资格
we lost our qualifying slot.
我们没有资格 就比不了赛
We don't qualify, we don't race.
相信我 各位 我正在处理 好吗
Believe me, guys, I'm working on it, okay?
赛车委员会以为因为Jared的事情
The racing committee assumed we weren't racing
我们不参赛了
because of what happened to Jared.
如果我们不参赛 就拿不到分
If we don't race, we don't get points.
听着 我知道这对你来说很不容易 但是
Look, I know this is a hard time for you, but…
别担心 我会处理的
Don't worry, I'm on it!
Harrison Cal
Harrison, Cal,
这些是联邦探员
these are federal agents.
他们正在调查那起车祸
They're investigating the crash.
调查什么
Investigating what?
我还以为那是个意外
I thought it was an accident.
是啊 我们还不太确定
Yeah, we're not so sure.
去吧 准备好 我会给我们拿到资格
Go, get ready. I'll get us a slot.
抱歉 我得回去干活了 各位
Sorry, I gotta get back to work, guys.
哇哦 不行 除非你告诉我们
Whoa. No, not until you tell us
你和Jared的父亲在隐瞒什么
what you and Jared's father are hiding.
我们知道Jared曾被捅伤 我们知道有超过10万美金
We know Jared was stabbed. We know he had over $100,000
失窃现金在他的车库里 我们还知道你不可能
of stolen money in his garage, and we know there's no way
对这事毫不知情
that you didn't know something about this.
目前情况对Jared来说
And this does not look good
非常不利 Dana
for Jared right now, Dana.
如果你在乎他 你得帮助我们
If you care about him, you'll help us.
我也希望我可以
I wish I could.
如果你是在害怕什么
If you're scared for some reason,
我们会保护你
we can protect you.
但如果我们发现你知情不报
But if we find out you're withholding anything,
我们必须逮捕你
we have to arrest you.
我得走了
I have to go.
拜托
Please.
一定是有什么秘密
That must be one hell of a secret.
是啊
Yeah.
Sebastian发来短信
A text from Sebastian.
Christopher要他告诉我们
It says that Christopher wanted him to tell us
Jared确定是被谋杀的
that Jared was definitely murdered.
Chris去哪儿了
So where's Chris?
问得好
Good question.
嘿 Christopher
Hey, Christopher.
你给我发了个信息就走了
So you just send me a text and then leave?
我不想再打扰你
I don't want to bother you
已经够麻烦你了
any more than I already have.
打扰我
Bother me?
这就是你对你所作所为的说辞么
Is that what you call what you did?
噢 Chris 我很抱歉
Oh, Chris, I'm so sorry.
我 我不该这样做的
I-I shouldn't have done it.
听着 我不明白
Look, I don't understand.
我把你带过来
I took you in,
我试着做正确的事情
I tried to do the right thing,
相信Tucker是我的孩子
believed Tucker was mine.
你为什么要因此说谎呢
Why did you lie about it?
我想我那时只是绝望了
I guess I was just desperate.
你知道 逃离Darrell
You know, to get away from Darrell,
给Tucker找个善待他的父亲 我
to try and find a good daddy for Tucker, I…
逃离Darrell 什么 他
Get away from Darrell? What, did…
他有没有伤害你
did he try to hurt you or something?
让我们 没有
Let's just… no.
Melody 你得给我说说
Melody, you gotta talk to me.
到底怎么了
What's going on?
Darrell脾气不好 我太害怕了
Darrell has a temper, and I was afraid.
不仅是 不仅对我 对Tucker也一样
Not just… not just for me but for Tucker.
我尝试过申请针对他的限制令
I tried to get a restraining order against him,
但他们说 我得等到暴行真正发生后
but they said I had to wait until something bad happened.
我很害怕 我只是 我不知道该怎么办
And I was afraid, and I just-- I didn't know what to do.
我从来不想伤害你
I never meant to hurt you.
没事
Okay.
没事的 好吗
It's okay. Yeah?
别担心Darrell
Don't worry about Darrell.
他不会伤害你们的
He's not gonna hurt either one of you.
首先他的会计说 他通过
First his accountant said that he was laundering drug money
高现金业务来洗钱
through high-cash businesses.
这儿的餐厅都挺大的 对吧
Restaurants are big down here, right?
特别大
Huge.
其实我开始还是有点拒绝的
Kind of resisted them at first.
你知道的 我并不算是个吃货
As you know, I'm not much of a foodie.
是嘛 那你现在是了么
What, now you are?
其实吧 我是
As a matter of fact, I am.
在罗马的时候 对吗
When in Rome, right?
好吧 或许你可以帮我们缩小范围
Well, maybe you can help us narrow down
挑选几个主要候选餐厅
which restaurants are prime candidates.
好吧
Okay.
看看都有哪些餐厅
What do we got?
这个怎么样 Pat O'Brien's
How about this… Pat O'Brien's?
Pat O's 他们不是贩毒集团的人
Pat O's? No way they're cartel.
他们在法国区已经有数十年了
They've been in the Quarter for decades.
他们调制的飓风鸡尾酒爽翻了 会让你
Make a killer hurricane cocktail that'll…
你应该试一下
You should try one.
我来这儿不是为了鸡尾酒的 T
I'm not here for the cocktails, T.
好吧
Okay.
我们赶紧查清Garcia的案子然后回家吧
Let's just get Garcia and get back home.
我不确定我是否想回家
I'm not sure I want to go back home.
什么
Sorry?
我只是说 我不确定
I'm just saying I'm not sure.
十年前 你恨不得用最快的速度
Ten years ago, you couldn't get
逃的越远越好
far enough away from this place fast enough,
现在你却喜欢上这儿了吗
and now you like it?
我不明白 Tammy
I don't understand, Tammy.
这个贩毒集团的案子可是你的关键一案
This cartel case is your big shot.
Isler可以升官 你也会升官 这可是
Isler moves up, you move up. It's…
你一直挂在嘴边的你想拥有的生活
everything you've always said you wanted.
这难道不是我们分手的原因吗
Isn't that why we broke up?
这跟你和我没有关系 Hannah
This isn't about me and you, Hannah.
这仅仅是我的缘故
This is just about me.
但是 你说你不想继续我们之间的关系
Still, when you say you don't want to be
是因为你想要把精力都放在
in a relationship because you want to focus
-你的事业上 -我当时
on your career… And that's the way
就是这么觉得的
I felt at the time.
听着 我很珍惜
Look, I love
我们共同的曾经 你知道的
what we had together, you know that.
但是 你也知道 当我到了华盛顿特区后我想要逃跑
But, you also know I was running when I got to D.C.
我不知道我自己是谁了
I didn't know who I was.
继续调查Garcia吧 如果发现了什么向我汇报
Keep digging into Garcia, let me know if you find anything.
Hannah
Hannah…
哇哦
Whoa.
Pride 给我回电 关于你手上的案子
Pride, call me back. I think I just got
我刚刚有了重大发现
a big break on your case.
利用FBI的劫持专案组调查了在密苏里
Had FBI's Robbery Task Force see if there were
发生的其它抢劫案是否会与密西西比抢劫案的作案手法相匹配
any other robberies that matched the MOs of the one
发现类似案件两起 一个是奥兰多银行 一个在莫拜尔
in Mississippi: bank in Orlando, one in Mobile,
亚特兰大的装甲车 这其中都涉嫌了三个戴面具的持枪者
armored car in Atlanta. All involved three masked gunmen
有着攻击性武器和带他们跑路的司机
with assault weapons and a getaway driver.
跟这几天发生的大多数银行抢劫案很像啊
That pretty much matches most bank robberies these days.
对 但是如果我告诉你 他们中的每个人
Right. But what if I told you each one
也正好出现在同一所城市的
also happened to take place in the exact same city
赛车比赛呢
as a car race?
哈
Huh.
假设这帮强盗团伙
Suggesting that the heist crew
和赛车有联系
is connected to the racing circuit.
太多巧合让我们很难不这么猜测
Too much of a coincidence for it not to be.
我是说 不管是谁黑进了Jared的车
I mean, whoever hacked Jared's car
很显然他对赛车从里到外都很了解
obviously knew racecars inside and out.
是的 除了Jared是海军 而不是赛车手这点
Yeah, except Jared's a marine, not part of the circuit,
那为什么要黑进他的车呢
so why hack his car?
- 那个 我就不知道了 -只是好奇
- That, I don't know. - Just curious,
你是怎么知道Jared的车被人黑过
how'd you even know Jared's car was hacked?
不要看着我
Well, don't look at me.
我照你吩咐的没有跟她讲
I left her alone like you said.
我还是保留着NCIS电脑权限
I still have my NCIS computer access.
我想我会一直关注你的 你知道
Figured I'd keep tabs on you, you know,
以防什么意外出现
in case something popped up.
因为她很想念我们
'Cause she misses us.
Gregorio探员 嗨
Agent Gregorio! Hey!
-很高兴见到你 - 我也是 来假装你并不高兴见到我
- Good to see you. - You, too. Let's pretend you didn't.
在我因此丢掉工作之前
I have to get back to the Garcia case
我得回去到Garcia案子上了
before I don't have a case to get back to.
祝你们好运
Good luck!
我以为她很讨厌带馅煎饼的
I thought she hated beignets.
她确实不喜欢
She does.
所以 我们有四个抢劫案
So, we got four robberies,
都和赛车有联系
all connected to the racing circuit,
Jared的车库里发现了被抢的现金
marked money in Jared's garage.
Russ和Dana什么都不肯说
Neither Russ or Dana are talking.
很难相信他们不是抢劫银行的人
Hard not to think that they're the bank robbers.
是的 只是Dana看上去恐惧多余愧疚
Yeah, except Dana seemed more scared than guilty.
检查下Jared的出行记录
Check Jared's leave record.
看看在每次抢劫案中他都在哪
See where he was on each of the robberies.
明白
Copy that.
嗨 你可能想查一下
Hey, you might want to check,
看看他们中有没有谁是电脑专家
see if any of 'em are cyber geeks.
我对他们是如何操作这场
I dove into the specifics
车祸的细节进行了深究
of how they manipulated that car crash.
不管是谁做的 他都很厉害
Whoever did it, they are good.
我是说很厉害的门萨国际黑客水平
I'm talking Mensa hacker level good.
是 但是 Jared并没有参与抢劫
Yeah, but… it wasn't Jared.
根据海军记录
According to the marines,
四起案件中 有三起案件发生的时候他在执行临时任务
he was TDY on three of the four robberies.
所以他不可能是团伙中的一员
So he couldn't have been a part of the crew.
或许他发现了这一切
Maybe he found out about it
想要做正确的事
and tried to do the right thing
却提前被人杀害了
and got killed before he could.
还是不能解释为什么他被捅伤
Still doesn't explain why he got stabbed
为什么Dana这么恐惧什么都不肯说
or why Dana was too scared to talk.
或许我们现在应该去找他父亲谈谈了
Maybe we ought to take another run at the father now?
这次带上搜查令
This time with a warrant.
把他带回来问话吧
Let's bring him in.
深挖每一支
Deep-dive every team
参加比赛的队伍 Patton
that competed in those races, Patton.
尤其是Dana的队伍
Especially Dana's.
我希望一个黑客可以找到另一个黑客
I'm hoping that a hacker can find a fellow hacker.
拜托 哥们 那不就是我的活么
Come on, man. That's what I'm all about.
这就是为什么我干这行
That's why I do what I do.
好吧 去查吧
Well, go do it.
接电话啊 Christopher
Come on, Christopher.
你到底在哪儿啊
Where the hell are you?
嗨
Hey.
你跑这儿来干嘛
What the hell are you doing here?
我是来给你一个友好的警告
I come here to give you a friendly warning.
离Tucker和他的妈妈远点
Stay away from Tucker and his mom.
-你明白了吗 -什么
- You understand? - What?
赶紧走吧 好吗
Get out of here, right…
但我并不认为你听进去我的话了
But I don't think you heard me.
听着 我可能不是Tucker的父亲
Look, I may not be Tucker's dad,
但我决不允许他 或是他妈妈
but I'm not gonna let anything happen to him
有任何闪失
or his mom.
所以 如果我是你
So, if I were you,
我就会 离他们远远的
I would just… stay away.
-不然呢 -相信我
- Or what? - Well, trust me.
你不会想知道的
You don't want to find out.
你知道的 那是我的儿子和我的女人
You see, that's my boy and my woman.
所以 为什么你他妈的不离远点呢
So, why don't you stay the hell away from them?
哦 你要扭断我的胳膊了
Ow! You're gonna bust my arm.
听着 我是不会警告你第二次的 你听到了吗
Look, I'm not warning you again. You hear me?
-你最好离他们远点 - 嗨
- You stay away from them. - Hey!
发生什么了
What's going on?
你的机工长 Cal Vernon
Your crew chief, Cal Vernon.
有三次入室盗窃的前科
Three priors for burglary.
你的技术专家 Nathan St. Clair
Your tech specialist, Nathan St. Clair,
曾经黑入过美国国防部服务器
served time for hacking a DoD server,
还有两个技工
and two mechanics,
你和Ansel Dane
you and Ansel Dane,
也都有前科
also have priors.
你们队伍一半的人都有前科
Half your team's got a record.
除此之外 我们知道Warbury赛车队
Plus, we know Warbury Racing
在四座发生抢劫案的城市里参加了四场比赛
competed in four cities where four robberies took place.
嗯 这说明不了什么
Mm… That don't mean nothing.
我说呀
Come on.
Connors
Connors.
为什么你一直在保护那些
Why do you keep protecting the people
该为你儿子的死负责的人呢
responsible for your son's murder?
什么样的父亲会这么做呢
What kind of father does that?
你 你不明白
Y-You don't understand.
你试试看
Try us.
是因为和Dana有关吗
Is this about Dana?
是因为这个吗
Is that it?
Jared爱她胜过一切
Jared loved her more than anything.
她也爱他
And she loved him, too.
他原本都打算向她求婚了
He was gonna propose to her.
这跟案子有什么关系么
What's that got to do with anything?
太有关系了
It's got everything to do with it!
Jared可以为Dana做任何事
Jared would do anything for Dana,
她也很清楚这一点
and she knew it, too.
所以她才从
That's why she wanted
原有的生活中解脱 找到新的出路
to straighten out her life, l-look for a way out.
Dana曾是抢劫团伙中的一员
Dana was part of the heist crew.
是 但是 她想金盆洗手
Yeah, but… but she wanted to quit.
为了Jared
For Jared.
但是那伙人不同意
Except they wouldn't let her.
他们是谁 那伙人还有谁
Who's they? The rest of the team?
不 不 不 也不是每个人都受此牵连
No, no, no. Not everyone was involved.
我也没跟他们一伙
I wasn't either.
我之前一直不知道
I didn't know about the robberies
直到Dana在医院跟坦白抢劫这事儿
until Dana told me at the hospital.
我发誓
I swear.
那Dana在抢劫团伙里是做什么的呢
So, what was Dana's job on the crew?
她是负责跑路的司机 但正如我刚才所言
She was the getaway driver, but like I said,
她不想再干了 她还威胁他们说
she wanted out, she threatened to come clean
如果不让她撤伙就告发他们
if they didn't let her go.
所以 他们就捅伤了Jared
So, what, they stabbed Jared
以示警告
to warn her?
他们发现Dana
They found out that Dana
打算把抢劫的事实和盘托出
was gonna tell him the truth about the heists.
她劝Jared别去医院
She convinced Jared not to go to the hospital,
否则他会伤得更严重
so he wouldn't get hurt worse.
Dana也不能跟Jared实话实说
Dana couldn't tell Jared the truth, either.
她只是让他相信她
She just asked him to… to trust her.
抢来的钱就放在Jared的车库里
And the money in Jared's garage.
那些钱是她的那份
It was her cut.
她决定告诉
She decided to tell…
Jared实情
Jared the truth
这周末
this weekend and…
那伙人却发现了
somehow they found out.
所以就动手杀了Jared
Which is why they killed Jared.
他们 还威胁要把她也杀了
And they… and they threatened to kill her and, um…
还要杀我 如果
and me, too, if…
如果她还继续生事的话
if she tried anything else.
所以我才不敢告诉你实话
That's why I was afraid to tell you the truth.
他们邪恶至极
They're vicious.
如果他说的都是事实 我们得找到Dana
Well, if he's telling the truth, we need to find Dana
保护她 我们现在就动身过去
and protect her. That's where we're headed.
Christopher 你到底上哪儿去了
Christopher, where the hell have you been?
我找了你好几个小时了
I've been trying to get a hold of you for hours.
我知道 King 对不起 我回去再跟你解释
I know, King, I'm sorry, and I'll explain it when I get in.
等下 等下 等下 你在哪 离赛车场近么
Wait, wait, wait. Where are you? Are you anywhere near the track?
Avondale大街 也就5到10分钟的车程吧 怎么了
Avondale, maybe five, ten minutes, why?
好 你现在赶紧去赛车场
Okay. I need you to head over there as fast as possible,
对Dana Wells实行保护性监禁 必要的话先逮捕她
take Dana Wells into protective custody. Arrest her
把她从那儿弄出来就行
if you have to, just get her out of there,
别当着她队友的面
and don't do it in front of any of her crew.
你到这了我再跟你说详情
I'll fill you in when you get here.
没问题
You got it.
Wells女士 Wells女士
Ms. Wells? Ms. Wells?
怎么了 Chris
Yeah, Chris.
King 我们来晚了
King, I think we're too late.
-什么意思 -看上去Dana已经被带走了
- What do you mean? - Looks like Dana's been taken.
赛车场的监控录像视角很宽
Track surveillance camera has a pretty wide angle,
就是这几个人把Dana带上了那辆黑色的道奇战马
but those are our guys forcing Dana into that black Charger.
发布这辆车的协查通告
Add the car to the BOLOs.
从今早上开始 没有人见过Vernon Dane
Nobody's seen Vernon, Dane,
还有 St. Clair
or St. Clair since this morning.
连今天比赛的赛前检查都没出现
Didn't even show up to pre-check for today's race.
他们肯定知道我们已经盯上他们了
They must know that we're onto them.
恩 如果是这样的话 Dana可能已经死了
Yeah. And if so, Dana could already be dead.
不一定
Maybe not.
我用我高超的技术
I hit Dana's e-mails and text messages
黑进了Dana的邮件和短信
with some Triple P-grade hacking of my own.
她不仅是赛车比赛的资深协调者
Turns out, she's not just the advance coordinator
也是抢劫案的策划者
for the races, she's the advance planner for the robberies.
有道理
Well, it makes sense.
资深协调者会提前一周到达
Advance coordinators go to the next town
比赛所在地的城市
a week ahead of each race.
这就为抢劫提供了充足的准备时间
That's plenty of time to prep for the next heist,
而且也是完美的掩饰
and it's a perfect cover, too.
这条短信表明他们
And that text indicates that they're planning
今天要在我们城里策划一场抢劫案
a hit today, in our town.
你知道在哪么
You know where?
我追踪不到她的
She left the location
任何电子通讯信号了
out of the digiverse.
你觉得他们把Dana截走
You think they took Dana to pull off
-去完成另一起抢劫案么 -如果是这样的
- one more heist? - If they did,
他们肯定采取了强迫手段
then they did it by force.
也就是说
Means figuring out
找到那伙抢劫犯
where the heist is gonna go down
就是我们唯一能救出Dana的机会了
might be our only chance to save her.
哦 我们得缩小区域内的潜在目标了
Oh, we'll narrow down possible targets in the area.
不
No.
Percy和Patton可以搞定
Percy and Patton can do that.
让Sebastian追查
Have Sebastian see if he can figure out
那些图上蓝点的目的地
what those schematics and blueprints go to.
那我干什么呢
Well, what does that leave me?
我们谈谈吧
Let's talk.
我知道 King 我搞砸了
I know, King, I messed up.
你可不仅仅是搞砸了 Christopher
You did more than that, Christopher.
在案件调查过程中失踪
Bad enough you went M.I.A. in the middle of a case…
仅此一次 下不为例 明白么
and that can't ever happen again, understand?
下不为例 但是
It won't, but…
新奥尔良警察局打电话过来了
NOPD called,
说Darrell控告
said Darrell filed
你袭击他
assault charges against you.
什么
What?
他先打我的
He swung at me first.
是的 幸运的是警方找到了目击证人
Yeah, well, lucky they found a witness who said
和你的说辞一致 但这些并不能
the same thing, but that doesn't explain
解释你为什么出现在那里
what you were doing there in the first place.
是这样 Melody曾试着申请针对他的
Look, Melody tried to get a restraining order
限制令
on him, all right?
她很担心自己和Tucker的安危
Said she was worried for both her and Tucker.
所以呢 你觉得
So, what, you thought
你得自己搞定这事儿
you-you'd handle it yourself,
于是就去恐吓他了
threaten him?
我做了
Well, I did what
我应该做的
needed to be done.
我见过你怎么做的
I've seen you go off-book…
别把我扯进来
Not about me.
你变了 Christopher
This isn't you, Christopher.
也许你以前是这样的
Maybe who you used to be,
但这不该是你现在的样子
but this is not who you've become.
情感问题 我懂的
Emotional situation, I get it,
但是你不能这么毛躁地冲过去就要解决问题
but you can't just go running off hotheaded to solve problems,
不能再这样了
not anymore.
我知道
I know.
你得想明白你要什么
You got to think about what it is you want.
你想以某种方式
You hoping to keep…
把Tucker
Tucker in your life
留在你的生命里么
some way?
我不知道
I don't know.
我知道我想给他最好的
I know I want what's best for him.
但有件事儿我绝对可以做
But there's one thing I can do
就是保护他不受Darrell的伤害
and that's protect them from Darrell.
那就想办法
Then figure out how to do that.
肯定会有正确的办法来解决 Christopher
There's a right way to handle this, Christopher.
找到它
Find it.
这个金融产品经理Simon Delaney呢
What about this financial manager, Simon Delaney?
恩 有什么线索么
Okay. Anything?
有 在这儿
Yeah, here it is.
Simon Delaney
Simon Delaney.
他显然还是
Apparently, he's also an officer
跟Garcia有关的三家公司的工作人员
of three other LLCs connected to Garcia.
也就是说这三家公司有可能牵扯到毒品洗钱
Which means three more possible drug-laundering companies.
Garcia的名字在法人文件上吗
Is Garcia's name on the title?
我得找找了 若是如此
I'll have to find out, but if so…
我们就有足够的证据提起诉讼了
We might have enough for an indictment.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
特别探员Pride打电话
There's a Special Agent Pride
找你
on the phone for you.
Percy刚刚也打电话来了
Percy just called, too.
肯定有什么重要的事儿
Must be important.
对不起
I'm sorry.
-我得去看看 -Tammy
I got to find out. Tammy…
不是有意打扰你
Wouldn't have bothered you,
不过我们认为有人有生命危险
but we think somebody's life may be at stake.
希望FBI的资源能够帮助我们
Hoping FBI resources can help.
没问题 你需要什么
Of course, what do you need?
你对赛车场案件的判断是对的
Well, you were right about the racing circuit.
我们确定了抢劫团伙的身份
We've IDed the heist crew
我们认为另一场抢劫可能即将发生
and we think another robbery may be imminent.
Patton拿到了设计蓝图和电路图
Yeah, Patton got blueprints and schematics,
但我们只能知道这是一条
but the best we can figure out is that it's a road map
指向某一IP地址的公路图
to certain IP addresses.
具体来说 这些地址
Specifically, the ones that relate
与Arsenal Protection公司研发的
to high-tech communication systems
高科技通讯系统有关
made by Arsenal Protection.
显然 他们把这些东西安装在运钞车上
Apparently, they install them in armored trucks
才可以让他们全天候监视安全总部
to allow continuous monitoring from security HQ.
问题是 我们不知道
You know, the problem is, we can't figure out
哪几家银行和Arsenal公司
which banks contracted
签了这份系统的合同
with Arsenal for the system.
希望银行抢劫案特勤组的数据库
Hoped Bank Robbery Task Force database
会有这方面的信息
might have that information.
让我看看
Let me see.
查过所有的本地银行了 没什么问题
Checked all local banks-- no issues
而且他们也快到关门下班了
and they're all closed for the day now.
所有的运钞车都回库了
Yeah, and all the armored trucks
正在做清点
are in and accounted for.
你看 我们…已经没有办法了
Look, we're… running out of options.
你们查过美联储的运钞车了吗
Did you check Federal Reserve trucks?
美联储吗
The Reserve?
这些家伙总不会疯狂到
No way these guys are crazy enough
抢劫政府的东西吧 对吧
to go after the feds, are they?
开车
Drive.
Patton还在追踪运钞车吗
Patton still tracking the armored truck?
他们还没有黑进去
They haven't hacked into it yet.
车子还在移动
The truck's still moving.
半英里开外
Half mile ahead.
支援什么时候到
When is backup arriving?
抢劫团伙可能监视着警用通讯频道
Crew could be monitoring police communications.
通知他们太过冒险 尤其是对Dana而言
Too risky to call, especially for Dana.
你们转进Magnolia大街 我们前后夹击
Cut over to Magnolia, we'll box them in.
小心点 我想我们被跟踪了
Heads up! I think we're being followed.
快汇报
Call it in.
-你干嘛呢 -不是我
- What're you doing? - Wasn't me.
这车就这么停了下来
The truck just shut down.
敢动一下你就死定了
Move and you're dead.
开锁 快
Locks! Now!
-下来 -别 别激动
- Come on! - Take it, take it easy.
-快走 -好 好的
- Move it! - Okay, okay, all right, all right.
快去拿钱
Get the money!
快跑 跑
Go, go, go!
NCIS
NCIS!
交给我了 快去追Dana
I got this. Go get Dana.
等等 她是不是在给我们发信号
Wait, i-is she signaling us?
她想让我们从侧面上
She wants us to cut around.
为什么
Why?
只有一种方法才能知道
One way to find out.
抓紧了
Hang on.
他们干嘛呢
What are they doing?
联邦探员
Federal agents!
举起手来 从车里出来
Hands up! Get out the car!
你还好吗 Dana
You okay, Dana?
还行吧 大概
Yeah, I think so.
车技不错
Nice driving.
你也是
You, too.
我们无法保证Dana可以逃脱牢狱之灾
Can't guarantee Dana won't spend some time
Connors先生
behind bars, Mr. Connors.
因为 毕竟 她曾经和他们是同谋
I mean, after all, she was complicit until she wasn't.
恩 我知道
Yeah, I know.
但我和联邦检察官说过了
But I spoke to the federal prosecutors,
告诉他们 她帮我们抓获抢劫团伙的所有事情
told them everything she did to help us bring down the crew.
加上 她也很配合调查
Plus, she's cooperating,
因此我还是很有信心的
so I'm hopeful.
至少不管如何
At least one way or the other,
她得到了解放…
she's out from underneath it…
终于…
finally…
平安无事
and safe.
我只求这么多
That's all I wanted.
Jared也会这么想的
That's all Jared would've wanted.
保重
Take care.
恩
Yeah.
可怜的人呐
Poor dude.
他经历的太多了
He's been through a lot.
还会经历更多
Gonna go through a lot more, too.
丧子之痛 无以复加
Losing a child, nothing harder.
我有点理解他的感受
Sort of know how he feels.
但是…
Still…
我们的确做得很好
we did a lot of good…
尤其是在我们人手不足的时候
especially considering we're down a man.
我以你们为荣
I'm proud of you.
对 不过我没觉得
Yeah, but I didn't feel
我们少一个人
like we were down a man, though,
因为每个人都参与了进来
the way everybody was pitching in.
还蛮不错的
It was kind of cool.
Gregorio也没被解雇
Didn't get Gregorio fired, either.
只是就目前情况来看
As far as we know.
一旦Sebastian通过训练
Well, we'll finally get back up to speed
我们就能够恢复以前的状态了
once Sebastian gets through training.
同时…
In the meantime…
我们休假一天
let's take the day off.
我觉得很好啊
Now, that works for me.
老兄 我都能
Man, I can just
听到靶场在呼唤着我的名字
hear that firing range calling my name.
天哪
Geez.
你怎么办
What about you?
我想你懂的
I think you know.
嗨
Hey.
你认为我们能够提起诉讼吗
Think we have enough for an indictment?
等我回来的时候告诉你 但我不抱乐观态度
I'll let you know when I get back, but I doubt it.
我们仍然需要确凿的证据
We are still looking for the smoking gun
将Garcia与NOLA交易直接联系起来
to directly link Garcia to NOLA businesses.
新奥尔良
New Orleans.
自从你来到这儿之后
You really have changed
你的确变了 对吧
since you've been down here, haven't you?
怎么说
How so?
你看上去更开心了…
You seem happier…
这是件好事
which is a good thing.
可能对我们来说不是好事 但对你 绝对是好事
Not for us, maybe, but for you, definitely.
可能
Maybe…
你终于可以停下奔波
you finally have stopped running.
我也这么想
I think so.
但是 工作方面
Still, what are you
你要怎么处理
gonna do for work?
NCIS的位置已经满了
NCIS slot's already filled.
我不知道
I don't know.
我之前一直在想 我可以试着说服Isler
I was thinking I'd try talking Isler
把我调到这儿
into transferring me here.
祝你好运 Isler需要你
Good luck. Isler needs you.
他可不会轻易把你拱手让人
He's not gonna let you go that easily.
要是他不放手 我就倒霉了
Yeah, well, if he doesn't, I'm screwed.
好吧…
Well…
…祝你好运
…good luck.
警察到这儿来做什么
What-what are the police doing here?
不要紧的 他们来这儿只是为了
Oh, it's no big deal-- they're just here in case
防止Darrell在你离开前就出现
Darrell shows up before you leave.
但他怎么知道我们要走了
But how does he know that we're leaving?
哦 他可能已经听说了
Oh, a little birdie might've told him.
什么
What?
听着 Melody
Look, Melody…
你不必再去担心他了 我保证
you don't have to worry about him anymore, I promise.
为什么 你要做什么
Why, what are you gonna do?
做该做的事
What needs to be done.
你呆在这儿
All right, you stay here.
你把Tucker放在车里
You put Tucker in the car.
我马上就回来 好吗
I'll be right back, all right?
发生什么了 啊
What's going on, huh?
他们要逮捕你 Darrell
They're arresting you, Darrell.
你们要干嘛
Hey, what're you doing?
放开我
Get off me.
我做了背景调查
I did a background search.
德克萨斯州有未执行的关于你的逮捕令
You got outstanding warrants in Texas.
加上袭击联邦官员
That, plus assaulting a federal officer,
你估计要在牢里呆很久了
you'll be going away for a long time.
安分点 把手放在身后
Settle down, hands behind your back!
这不对 好吗
This ain't right, okay?
你们不能这么对我
You can't do this to me.
已经做了
Already did.
我告诉过你离他们远点
I told you to stay away from them
我是认真的
and I meant it.
走吧 把他带走
Now, go on, get him out of here.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
没什么好说的
There's nothing to say.
你来向我求助 不是吗
You came to me for help, right?
或许事情没有朝着
It may not have turned out the way
我们两个人设想的方向发展 但…
either of us wanted it to, but…
事实证明
it's how it turned out
结果是好的
and it's all right.
我能理解你这么做的原因
I understand why you did what you did
真的
I do…
而且
and besides…
我不得不把自己想象成一个父亲
I got to imagine myself being a daddy.
我喜欢这种感觉
I like how it feels.
谢谢你
Thank you.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
===GA字幕组===
翻译：睡不够的饭团、Lily、鸡血、echo、Sally、诸事不顺的栗子
校对：阿珂姑娘、流年
总校：流年
分配：鸡血
时间轴&统筹：栗子
===本集吐槽===
===Sebastian=话唠，啊哈哈哈===
===LaSalle肯定是老司机啊，你还记得东京漂移嘛===
===断背山下 百合花开===
===猝不及防===